Guide to the Max S. Baucus Papers 1958-2016 (bulk 1974-2014)
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Senate: Press, 1978-2014; Series VIII; 41.1 linear feet; 15.3 gigabytes
  - Press Clips, 1978-2014; Sub-series 1; 23.6 linear feet
    - Press clips, September 11-November 1997 (Box-folder Series 8 - 34/7)
    - Press clips, December 1997-January 20, 1998 (Box-folder Series 8 - 34/8)
    - Press clips, January 21-February 10, 1998 (Box-folder Series 8 - 34/9)
    - Press clips, February 11-28, 1998 (Box-folder Series 8 - 35/1)
    - Press clips, March 1-16, 1998 (Box-folder Series 8 - 35/2)
    - Press clips, March 17-31, 1998 (Box-folder Series 8 - 35/3)
    - Press clips, April 1-20, 1998 (Box-folder Series 8 - 35/4)
    - Press clips, April 21-May 14, 1998 (Box-folder Series 8 - 35/5)
    - Press clips, May 15-31, 1998 (Box-folder Series 8 - 35/6)
    - Press clips, June-July 2, 1998 (Box-folder Series 8 - 35/7)
    - Press clips, July 3-15, 1998 (Box-folder Series 8 - 35/8)
    - Press clips, July 16-August 4, 1998 (Box-folder Series 8 - 35/9)
    - Press clips, August 5-31, 1998 (Box-folder Series 8 - 36/1)
    - Press clips, September-October 21, 1998 (Box-folder Series 8 - 36/2)
    - Press clips, October 22-November 20, 1998 (Box-folder Series 8 - 36/3)
    - Press clips, November 21-December 20, 1998 (Box-folder Series 8 - 36/4)
    - Press clips, December 21, 1998-January 20, 1999 (Box-folder Series 8 - 36/5)
    - Press clips, January 21-February 10, 1999 (Box-folder Series 8 - 36/6)
    - Press clips, February 11-29, 1999 (Box-folder Series 8 - 36/7)
    - Press clips, March 1-20, 1999 (Box-folder Series 8 - 36/8)
    - Press clips, March 21-April 31, 1999 (Box-folder Series 8 - 36/9)
    - Press clips, May 1-20, 1999 (Box-folder Series 8 - 37/1)
    - Press clips, May 21-June 1999 (Box-folder Series 8 - 37/2)
    - Press clips, July-August 10, 1999 (Box-folder Series 8 - 37/3)
    - Press clips, August 11-September 9, 1999 (Box-folder Series 8 - 37/4)
    - Press clips, September 10-23, 1999 (Box-folder Series 8 - 37/5)
    - Press clips, September 24-October 20, 1999 (Box-folder Series 8 - 37/6)
    - Press clips, 1999 (Box-folder Series 8 - 37/7)
    - Press clips, 1999 (Box-folder Series 8 - 37/8)
    - Press clips, 1999 (Box-folder Series 8 - 37/9)
    - Press clips, October 21, 1999-January 2000 (Box-folder Series 8 - 37/10)
    - Press clips, February 1-20, 1000 (Box-folder Series 8 - 38/1)
    - Press clips, February 21-March 10, 2000 (Box-folder Series 8 - 38/2)
    - Press clips, March 11-April 14, 2000 (Box-folder Series 8 - 38/3)
    - Press clips, April 15-May 2000 (Box-folder Series 8 - 38/4)
    - Press clips, June 1-26, 2000 (Box-folder Series 8 - 38/5)
    - Press clips, June 27-July 13, 2000 (Box-folder Series 8 - 38/6)
    - Press clips, July 14-31, 2000 (Box-folder Series 8 - 38/7)
    - Press clips, August-September 2000 (Box-folder Series 8 - 38/8)
    - Press clips, October 1-20, 2000 (Box-folder Series 8 - 38/9)
    - Press clips, October 21-December 3, 2000 (Box-folder Series 8 - 39/1)
    - Press clips, December 4, 2000-June 2001 (Box-folder Series 8 - 39/2)
    - Press clips, July-November 17, 2001 (Box-folder Series 8 - 39/3)
    - Press clips, November 18, 2001-January 12, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 39/4)
    - Press clips, January 13-31, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 39/5)
    - Press clips, February 1-10, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 39/6)
    - Press clips, February 11-28, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 39/7)
    - Press clips, March 1-18, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 39/8)
    - Press clips, March 19-31, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 39/9)
    - Press clips, April 1-13, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 40/1)
    - Press clips, April 14-May 5, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 40/2)
    - Press clips, May 6-31, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 40/3)
    - Press clips, June 1-15, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 40/4)
    - Press clips, June 16-July 2, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 40/5)
    - Press clips, July 3-25, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 40/6)
    - Press clips, July 26-August 10, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 40/7)
    - Press clips, August 11-24, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 40/8)
    - Press clips, August 25-September 6, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 40/9)
    - Press clips, September 7-15, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 41/1)
    - Press clips, September 16-October 2, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 41/2)
    - Press clips, October 3-11, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 41/3)
    - Press clips, October 12-19, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 41/4)
    - Press clips, October 20-31, 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 41/5)
    - Press clips, November-December 2002 (Box-folder Series 8 - 41/6)
    - Press clips, January-February 2003 (Box-folder Series 8 - 41/7)
    - Press clips, March 2003 (Box-folder Series 8 - 41/8)
    - Press clips, April-May 15, 2003 (Box-folder Series 8 - 41/9)
    - Press clips, May 16-June 6, 2003 (Box-folder Series 8 - 42/1)
    - Press clips, June 7-26, 2003 (Box-folder Series 8 - 42/2)
    - Press clips, June 27-July 25, 2003 (Box-folder Series 8 - 42/3)
    - Press clips, July 26-September 10, 2003 (Box-folder Series 8 - 42/4)
    - Press clips, September 11-October 3, 2003 (Box-folder Series 8 - 42/5)
    - Press clips, October 4-31, 2003 (Box-folder Series 8 - 42/6)
    - Press clips, November 1-20, 2003 (Box-folder Series 8 - 42/7)
    - Press clips, November 21, 2003-January 10, 2004 (Box-folder Series 8 - 42/8)
    - Press clips, January 11-31, 2004 (Box-folder Series 8 - 42/9)
    - Press clips, February 2004 (Box-folder Series 8 - 43/1)
    - Press clips, March 1-18, 2004 (Box-folder Series 8 - 43/2)
    - Press clips, March 19-April 10, 2004 (Box-folder Series 8 - 43/3)
    - Press clips, April 11-30, 2004 (Box-folder Series 8 - 43/4)
    - Press clips, May 1-18, 2004 (Box-folder Series 8 - 43/5)
    - Press clips, May 19-June 5, 2004 (Box-folder Series 8 - 43/6)
    - Press clips, June 6-24, 2004 (Box-folder Series 8 - 43/7)
    - Press clips, June 25-July 10, 2004 (Box-folder Series 8 - 43/8)
    - Press clips, July 11-August 31, 2004 (Box-folder Series 8 - 43/9)
    - Press clips, September 2004 (Box-folder Series 8 - 44/1)
    - Press clips, October 2004-January 10, 2005 (Box-folder Series 8 - 44/2)
    - Press clips, January 11-31, 2005 (Box-folder Series 8 - 44/3)
    - Press clips, February 1-10, 2005 (Box-folder Series 8 - 44/4)
    - Press clips, February 11-March 3, 2005 (Box-folder Series 8 - 44/5)
    - Press clips, March 4-31, 2005 (Box-folder Series 8 - 44/6)
    - Press clips, April-May 2005 (Box-folder Series 8 - 44/7)
    - Press clips, June 1-11, 2005 (Box-folder Series 8 - 44/8)
    - Press clips, June 12-21, 2005 (Box-folder Series 8 - 44/9)
    - Press clips, June 22-July 10, 2005 (Box-folder Series 8 - 45/1)
    - Press clips, July 11-August 11, 2005 (Box-folder Series 8 - 45/2)
    - Press clips, August 12-September 17, 2005 (Box-folder Series 8 - 45/3)
    - Press clips, September 18-October 6, 2005 (Box-folder Series 8 - 45/4)
    - Press clips, October 7-31, 2005 (Box-folder Series 8 - 45/5)
    - Press clips, November-December 2005 (Box-folder Series 8 - 45/6)
    - Press clips, January 1-11, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 45/7)
    - Press clips, January 12-21, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 45/8)
    - Press clips, January 22-February 4, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 45/9)
    - Press clips, February 5-15, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 45/10)
    - Press clips, February 16-22, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 46/1)
    - Press clips, February 23-March 8, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 46/2)
    - Press clips, March 9-28, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 46/3)
    - Press clips, March 29-April 20, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 46/4)
    - Press clips, April 21-May 10, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 46/5)
    - Press clips, May 11-June 5, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 46/6)
    - Press clips, June 6-July 20, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 46/7)
    - Press clips, July 21-August 5, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 46/8)
    - Press clips, August 5-20, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 46/9)
    - Press clips, August 21-September 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 47/1)
    - Press clips, October 1-27, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 47/2)
    - Press clips, October 28-November 11, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 47/3)
    - Press clips, November 12-December 4, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 47/4)
    - Press clips, December 5-31, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 47/5)
    - Press clips, January 1-15, 2006 (Box-folder Series 8 - 47/6)
    - Press clips, January 16-February 10, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 47/7)
    - Press clips, February 11-March 11, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 47/8)
    - Press clips, March 12-24, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 47/9)
    - Press clips, March 25-April 11, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 48/1)
    - Press clips, April 12-May 3, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 48/2)
    - Press clips, May 4-31, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 48/3)
    - Press clips, June 1-17, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 48/4)
    - Press clips, June 18-30, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 48/5)
    - Press clips, July 1-12, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 48/6)
    - Press clips, July 13-31, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 48/7)
    - Press clips, August-September 11, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 48/8)
    - Press clips, September 12-30, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 48/9)
    - Press clips, October 1-10, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 49/1)
    - Press clips, October 11-25, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 49/2)
    - Press clips, October 26-November 8, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 49/3)
    - Press clips, November 9-30, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 49/4)
    - Press clips, December 1-19, 2007 (Box-folder Series 8 - 49/5)
    - Press clips, December 20, 2007-January 17, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 49/6)
    - Press clips, January 18-31, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 49/7)
    - Press clips, February 1-13, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 49/8)
    - Press clips, February 14-26, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 50/1)
    - Press clips, February 27-March 9, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 50/2)
    - Press clips, March 10-16, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 50/3)
    - Press clips, March 17-25, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 50/4)
    - Press clips, March 26-April 8, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 50/5)
    - Press clips, April 9-23, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 50/6)
    - Press clips, April 24-May 11, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 50/7)
    - Press clips, May 11-22, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 50/8)
    - Press clips, May 23-June 3, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 50/9)
    - Press clips, June 4-11, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 51/1)
    - Press clips, June 12-21, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 51/2)
    - Press clips, June 22-July 2, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 51/3)
    - Press clips, July 3-10, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 51/4)
    - Press clips, July 11-25, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 51/5)
    - Press clips, July 26-August 12, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 51/6)
    - Press clips, August 13-September 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 51/7)
    - Press clips, October 1-20, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 51/8)
    - Press clips, October 21-November 3, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 51/9)
    - Press clips, November 4-26, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 52/1)
    - Press clips, November 27-December 14, 2008 (Box-folder Series 8 - 52/2)
    - Press clips, December 15, 2008-January 12, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 52/3)
    - Press clips, January 13-31, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 52/4)
    - Press clips, February 1-17, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 52/5)
    - Press clips, February 18-March 3, 009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 52/6)
    - Press clips, March 4-14, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 52/7)
    - Press clips, March 15-April 5, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 52/8)
    - Press clips, April 6-26, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 52/9)
    - Press clips, April 27-May 16, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 53/1)
    - Press clips, May 17-31, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 53/2)
    - Press clips, June 1-16, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 53/3)
    - Press clips, June 17-26, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 53/4)
    - Press clips, June 27-July 12, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 53/5)
    - Press clips, July 13-27, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 53/6)
    - Press clips, July 28-August 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 53/7)
    - Press clips, September 1-10, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 53/8)
    - Press clips, September 11-20, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 53/9)
    - Press clips, September 21-October 4, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 54/1)
    - Press clips, October 5-14, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 54/2)
    - Press clips, October 15-November 5, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 54/3)
    - Press clips, November 6-30, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 54/4)
    - Press clips, December 1-10, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 54/5)
    - Press clips, December 11-21, 2009 (Box-folder Series 8 - 54/6)
    - Press clips, December 22, 2009-January 10, 2010 (Box-folder Series 8 - 54/7)
    - Press clips, January 11-31, 2010 (Box-folder Series 8 - 54/8)
    - Press clips, February 1-20, 2010 (Box-folder Series 8 - 54/9)
    - Press clips, February 21-March 13, 2010 (Box-folder Series 8 - 55/1)
    - Press clips, March 14-31, 2010 (Box-folder Series 8 - 55/2)
    - Press clips, April 1-13, 2010 (Box-folder Series 8 - 55/3)
    - Press clips, April 14-May 2010 (Box-folder Series 8 - 55/4)
    - Press clips, June 1-16, 2010 (Box-folder Series 8 - 55/5)
    - Press clips, June 17-30, 2010 (Box-folder Series 8 - 55/6)
    - Press clips, July 1-20, 2010 (Box-folder Series 8 - 55/7)
    - Press clips, July 21-August 20, 2010 (Box-folder Series 8 - 55/8)
    - Press clips, August 21-September 10, 2010 (Box-folder Series 8 - 55/9)
    - Press clips, September 11-30, 2010 (Box-folder Series 8 - 56/1)
    - Press clips, October-November 10, 2010 (Box-folder Series 8 - 56/2)
    - Press clips, November 11-December 12, 2010 (Box-folder Series 8 - 56/3)
    - Press clips, December 13, 2010-January 20, 2011 (Box-folder Series 8 - 56/4)
    - Press clips, January 21-May 2011 (Box-folder Series 8 - 56/5)
    - Press clips, June-September 2011 (Box-folder Series 8 - 56/6)
    - Press clips, October-December 2011 (Box-folder Series 8 - 56/7)
    - Press clips, January-April 2012 (Box-folder Series 8 - 56/8)
    - Press clips, May-December 2012 (Box-folder Series 8 - 57/1)
    - Press clips, January-April 20, 2013 (Box-folder Series 8 - 57/2)
    - Press clips, April 21-July 2013 (Box-folder Series 8 - 57/3)
    - Press clips, August-October 2013 (Box-folder Series 8 - 57/4)
    - Press clips, November 2013-January 2014 (Box-folder Series 8 - 57/5)
    - Press clips, January 8, 2014 (Box-folder Series 8 - 57/6)
  - Press Releases, 1979-2014; Sub-series 2; 11.8 linear feet
    This subseries consists of prepared statements released by Max Baucus regarding legislation, current events, sponsored and cosponsored bills, and other political and legislative issues of the day. It also contains news headlines and summaries from Montana newspapers, which were filed with some early office press releases. Beginning in March of 1993 press releases were filed individually, with topics typed on individual folder labels. While press releases are listed here by date, a list of these topics is available upon request.
    - Press releases, February-July 1979 (Box-folder Series 8 - 57/7)
    - Press releases, August-December 1979 (Box-folder Series 8 - 57/8)
    - Press releases, January-March 1980 (Box-folder Series 8 - 57/9)
    - Press releases, April-June 1980 (Box-folder Series 8 - 57/10)
    - Press releases, July-December 1980 (Box-folder Series 8 - 58/1)
    - Press releases, January-February 1981 (Box-folder Series 8 - 58/2)
    - Press releases, March-May 1981 (Box-folder Series 8 - 58/3)
    - Press releases, June-August 1981 (Box-folder Series 8 - 58/4)
    - Press releases, September-November 1981 (Box-folder Series 8 - 58/5)
    - Press releases, December 1981-March 1982 (Box-folder Series 8 - 58/6)
    - Press releases, April-July 1982 (Box-folder Series 8 - 58/7)
    - Press releases, August-September 1982 (Box-folder Series 8 - 58/8)
    - Press releases, October 1982-January 11, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 58/9)
    - Press releases, January 12-31, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 59/1)
    - Press releases, February 1-19, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 59/2)
    - Press releases, February 20-March 11, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 59/3)
    - Press releases, March 12-28, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 59/4)
    - Press releases, March 29-April 13, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 59/5)
    - Press releases, April 14-29, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 59/6)
    - Press releases, May 1-16, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 59/7)
    - Press releases, May 17-31, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 59/8)
    - Press releases, June 1-23, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 59/9)
    - Press releases, June 24-July 9, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 60/1)
    - Press releases, July 10-26, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 60/2)
    - Press releases, July 27-August 16, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 60/3)
    - Press releases, August 17-September 11, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 60/4)
    - Press releases, September 12-27, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 60/5)
    - Press releases, September 28-October 19, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 60/6)
    - Press releases, October 20-November 9, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 60/7)
    - Press releases, November 10-30, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 60/8)
    - Press releases, December 1-22, 1983 (Box-folder Series 8 - 61/1)
    - Press releases, December 27, 1983-February 1984 (Box-folder Series 8 - 61/2)
    - Press releases, March-April 1984 (Box-folder Series 8 - 61/3)
    - Press releases, May-June 12, 1984 (Box-folder Series 8 - 61/4)
    - Press releases, June 13-July 1984 (Box-folder Series 8 - 61/5)
    - Press releases, August-September 1984 (Box-folder Series 8 - 61/6)
    - Press releases, October 1984-March 1985 (Box-folder Series 8 - 61/7)
    - Press releases, April-June 1985 (Box-folder Series 8 - 61/8)
    - Press releases, July-September 1985 (Box-folder Series 8 - 61/9)
    - Press releases, October-December 1985 (Box-folder Series 8 - 62/1)
    - Press releases, January-April 1986 (Box-folder Series 8 - 62/2)
    - Press releases, May-August 1986 (Box-folder Series 8 - 62/3)
    - Press releases, September 1986-March 1987 (Box-folder Series 8 - 62/4)
    - Press releases, April-August 1987 (Box-folder Series 8 - 62/5)
    - Press releases, September-December 1987 (Box-folder Series 8 - 62/6)
    - Press releases, February 1988-March 1989 (Box-folder Series 8 - 62/7)
    - Press releases, May-June 1989 (Box-folder Series 8 - 62/8)
    - Press releases, July-September 1989 (Box-folder Series 8 - 62/9)
    - Press releases, October-November 1989 (Box-folder Series 8 - 63/1)
    - Press releases, December 1989-February 1990 (Box-folder Series 8 - 63/2)
    - Press releases, March-June 1990 (Box-folder Series 8 - 63/3)
    - Press releases, July-September 1990 (Box-folder Series 8 - 63/4)
    - Press releases, October 1990-February 1991 (Box-folder Series 8 - 63/5)
    - Press releases, March-May 1991 (Box-folder Series 8 - 63/6)
    - Press releases, June-September 1991 (Box-folder Series 8 - 63/7)
    - Press releases, October 1991 (Box-folder Series 8 - 63/8)
    - Press releases, November-December 1991 (Box-folder Series 8 - 63/9)
    - Press releases, January 1992 (Box-folder Series 8 - 64/1)
    - Press releases, February 1992 (Box-folder Series 8 - 64/2)
    - Press releases, March-April 1992 (Box-folder Series 8 - 64/3)
    - Press releases, May 1992 (Box-folder Series 8 - 64/4)
    - Press releases, June 1992 (Box-folder Series 8 - 64/5)
    - Press releases, July 1992 (Box-folder Series 8 - 64/6)
    - Press releases, August-September 10, 1992 (Box-folder Series 8 - 64/7)
    - Press releases, September 11-December 4, 1992 (Box-folder Series 8 - 64/8)
    - Press releases, December 7, 1992-January 14, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 64/9)
    - Press releases, January 15-31, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 65/1)
    - Press releases, February 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 65/2)
    - Press releases, March 1-22, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 65/3)
    - Press releases, March 23-29, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 65/4)
    - Press releases, March 30-April 9, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 65/5)
    - Press releases, April 10-21, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 65/6)
    - Press releases, April 21-27, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 65/7)
    - Press releases, April 29-May 5, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 65/8)
    - Press releases, May 6-11, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 65/9)
    - Press releases, May 12-21, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 66/1)
    - Press releases, May 24-June 2, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 66/2)
    - Press releases, June 8-14, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 66/3)
    - Press releases, June 15-22, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 66/4)
    - Press releases, June 23-24, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 66/5)
    - Press releases, June 25-30, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 66/6)
    - Press releases, July 1-6, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 66/7)
    - Press releases, July 7-15, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 66/8)
    - Press releases, July 16-21, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 67/1)
    - Press releases, July 22-26, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 67/2)
    - Press releases, July 27-31, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 67/3)
    - Press releases, August 1-3, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 67/4)
    - Press releases, August 5, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 67/5)
    - Press releases, August 4-8. 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 67/6)
    - Press releases, August 9-15, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 67/7)
    - Press releases, August 16-31, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 67/8)
    - Press releases, September 2-10, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 67/9)
    - Press releases, September 13-15, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 68/1)
    - Press releases, September 18-28, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 68/2)
    - Press releases, September 29-October 13, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 68/3)
    - Press releases, October 14-31, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 68/4)
    - Press releases, November 1-23, 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 68/5)
    - Press releases, November 24-December 1993 (Box-folder Series 8 - 68/6)
    - Press releases, January 3-24, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 68/7)
    - Press releases, January 25-February 10, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 68/8)
    - Press releases, February 11-24, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 68/9)
    - Press releases, February 25-March 8, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 69/1)
    - Press releases, March 9-17, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 69/2)
    - Press releases, March 18-31, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 69/3)
    - Press releases, April 4-18, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 69/4)
    - Press releases, April 19-22, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 69/5)
    - Press releases, April 24-May 4, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 69/6)
    - Press releases, May 5-10, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 69/7)
    - Press releases, May 10-12, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 69/8)
    - Press releases, May 12-17, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 69/9)
    - Press releases, May 18-19, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 70/1)
    - Press releases, May 20-25, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 70/2)
    - Press releases, May 25-26, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 70/3)
    - Press releases, May 27-June 10, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 70/4)
    - Press releases, June 13-30, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 70/5)
    - Press releases, July 1-12, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 70/6)
    - Press releases, July 13-15, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 70/7)
    - Press releases, July 16-19, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 70/8)
    - Press releases, July 21-26, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 70/9)
    - Press releases, July 27-August 3, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 71/1)
    - Press releases, August 4-11, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 71/2)
    - Press releases, August 11-19, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 71/3)
    - Press releases, August 20-26, 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 71/4)
    - Press releases, August 26-September 1994 (Box-folder Series 8 - 71/5)